Guide to the Sam Adams Darcy Papers TAM 124
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Additional Correspondence
  - Correspondence: R, 1935-1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: S, 1948-1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Stein, Harry, 1966-1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: U, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: V, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: W, 1940-1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: X,Y,Z, 1925-1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Series VIII: Photographs and Graphics
  - 1928 Nomination Banquet of Communist Party, NYC (Box OS 001, Folder 4)
  - Acquaintances, portraits, events (Photographs and one negative), 1879-circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Burke, Jake; Daily Worker Cartoon (Furiers' Strike), undated (Box MSOS004, Folder 2)
  - Burck, Jake: Daily Worker Cartoon (Gastonia Strike), 1929 (Box MSOS004, Folder 2)
  - Burke, Jake: Daily Worker Cartoon (Organizing Workers), undated (Box MSOS004, Folder 2)
  - Burke, Jake: Daily Worker Cartoon (Peace), undated (Box MSOS004, Folder 2)
  - Burial of J.H. Bland, Philadelphia, 1939 (Box OS 001, Folder 4)
  - Burial of J.B. McNamara, undated (Box OS 001, Folder 4)
  - Graphics and Clippings (Strikes, Mother Jones, Frederick Douglass, etc.), undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Group involved in 1931 trial in Long Beach for conspiracy to commit criminal syndicalism (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Photographs of Newsprint Montages by Sam Darcy (includes San Francisco strikes, demonstrations, Mooney, Darcy trial), undated (Box OS 001, Folder 1-3)
  - Photo postcards (featuring prominent Russians and Marxists), undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Portraits, convention photos, circa 1940s (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Portrait of William Z. Foster, undated (Box OS 001, Folder 4)
  - Reference photocopies of exhibit boards, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Series IX: Unprocessed Materials, circa 1930-1998; 1960-1985
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order which they were received from the donor.
  Series 9 is comprised of materials that came to the repository after the initial donation was processed. Types of materials include manuscripts, articles, correspondence, and photographic and graphic materials. Much of the series is various drafts of the manuscript Tales of Three Worlds.
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 4, Folder 38-47)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 5-7)
  - Unprocessed photographic and graphic materials (Box 8)